Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
The Manipulated
[shuddering breaths]
TO PARK TAEJOONG
[breathing heavily]
Shit.
[screaming] Son of a bitch!
[screams]
[monitor beeping]
A GIFT HAS ARRIVED
PARK TAEJOONG
RAPE, MURDER
[sighs]
LOL
BAEK DOKYUNG IS THE REAL CULPRIT
NOW FIND BAEK DOKYUNG
I'LL GIVE YOU A HINT
[breathes deeply]
[chuckles softly]
Now it's time to follow the right path,
Park Taejoong. [chuckles]
BAEK DOKYUNG
Well, now, this should be fun.
Hope you're ready, Dokyung.
Sorry, but he needed the incentive.
He'll make his way over to you.
ACCOUNT PRIVACY
PRIVATE ACCOUNT
SWITCH TO PUBLIC
[sighs]
Hopefully he'll figure it all out quickly.
Now let the best man win.
[chuckles]
I'M IN BUSAN!
EVERYONE GATHER
Uh, we tried for two years.
Same result every time.
We kept visiting,
but Taejoong always refused.
So we've never even met with him once.
I don't hold it against him, though.
If I were in a prison uniform,
I wouldn't want my friends
to see me in it either.
Yeah, but we've known
each other for so long.
It's not like we'd abandon him
for something like that.
[Daehoon] I understand why
he wouldn't want us to visit.
It would make him feel worse
to be a burden.
I'm touched that you all speak so highly
of a guy who committed murder,
like he's still your friend.
Detective. You act like you know him,
but you don't.
We've been his friends forever.
Which is honestly why
we know for a fact
that he isn't a criminal.
How supportive.
He's lucky to have friends like you.
Sorry, why are you asking us
these types of things?
Why don't you go
ask him about it yourself?
Well, actually, protocol dictates
that we need to cover our bases--
Wait. Did something bad
happen to him, sir?
-Well...
-[Hwang] Don't worry.
We have everything under control.
If anything strange happens,
let me know right away.
Keep in touch, okay?
[under breath] How fucking useless.
Sorry to intrude. I appreciate the coffee.
Weird.
What's his problem?
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
[Taejoong] What happens
when I catch the real killer?
Park Taejoong?
Listen, you piece of shit!
-Hey! Give me back my--
-Back off!
[over PA] Smoking in the Busan Express
Bus Terminal is prohibited.
Thank you for your cooperation
and for using
the Busan Express Bus Terminal.
Fucking found him.
Let's go.
Hello... Uh...
But where are we going?
Busan.
Let Busan Terminal know
we're on our way there.
[indistinct announcements over PA]
[engine starts]
The Manipulated
[breath trembling]
[groans]
[groaning]
Shit, I missed.
Hey, my bad.
Bring it here.
Hmm.
[sniffs]
[whimpering]
You thought I wouldn't find you?
I'm so sorry, sir.
Please forgive me.
If I do that,
think of what the others will say.
"It's fine if we betray that guy."
"Don't worry. Nothing's gonna happen."
We can't have that. [chuckles]
Don't do this, please.
Okay. Stand up.
I'll keep you alive, okay?
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
Just spar me a little.
Ready?
[yells]
[groans]
[screams]
What's he up to?
Are you having fun without me again?
Well, I thought you were
in a different country by now.
The old man keeps telling me to go.
I don't feel like it.
Also, what would you do
without me? [chuckles]
You're right.
I'm glad you're here.
Let's go have a drink downstairs.
[Dokyung chuckles]
[♪ upbeat dance music playing]
When the hell are you
gonna open this place?
I feel like my investment's being wasted.
All the money I've pooled
from the other guys isn't enough.
I need help getting to the finish line.
You asshole. All you ever want to do
is talk about money.
Hey, I got you something.
[sniffs]
Whoa!
This is some good quality shit.
Fuck, yeah!
[exclaims]
[laughing]
[fizzing]
Hurry up and open this place already.
Trust me.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get what I need,
you woodpecker-looking motherfucker.
Yeah, yeah.
Just let me know how much you want.
Really?
I never doubted you.
I'm in the mood to party.
Get the biggest ship ready.
Okay, you got it.
Let's get wild tonight.
[exhales deeply]
[laughs]
ELECTRONICS REPAIR SHOP
[line ringing]
Why are you pacing around?
Did you get robbed?
No, I haven't been able
to get ahold of Taejoong.
[line ringing]
You didn't tell him to leave, did you?
No. He could have left
for his own reasons.
But all of his things are still here.
So why would he...
Did you increase the rent?
Really? I'm not some kind of lowlife.
Right. Sorry.
I hope everything's okay with him.
What if he was caught by the police?
Was he thrown back in prison?
Why don't we go check?
Check?
What do you mean?
[buzzer blares]
Can I...
[door beeps, unlocks]
-Have a good one.
-Thanks again.
-Hey.
-Is he there?
Judging by the answers I got from Father,
he hasn't been caught yet,
so that's good.
If he's not in here,
where the hell did he go?
[line ringing]
I'll keep calling.
Wait a minute.
What?
Isn't he borrowing one of your phones?
[inhales sharply]
-So you're looking for a lost phone?
-Yes.
Whose is it?
It's my phone.
But a thief ran off with it.
Did you let the authorities know?
Not yet. I thought it'd be a hassle.
Can you turn on location sharing?
Sure. ID, please.
Oh, sure.
Here.
-Would you write down the number for me?
-Okay.
Here.
What?
[sighs] What was that?
[sniffles]
So, does it show where he is?
Says he's in Busan right now.
Really?
TAEJOONG
BUSAN METROPOLITAN CITY
All right. Good work.
Verify the location, text it to me, okay?
-[clears throat]
-Looks like I'm pretty good at my job.
What do you mean?
I decided to track Noh Yongsik's location,
and two phones showed up.
Both are in Busan.
I suspect Noh Yongsik has one of them.
But as for the second one,
it's probably with Park Taejoong.
[chuckles] This is too easy.
I mean, so is Noh Yongsik also a suspect?
[laughing]
Well, you know,
I can't leave any stones unturned.
[cell phone beeps]
[cell phone vibrates]
Park Taejoong's whereabouts
have been found.
BUSAN TERMINAL AREA B
[Taejoong] What happens
when I catch the real killer?
Park Taejoong?
I needed to prove my innocence.
So I'm at the culprit's location now.
LOCKER NUMBER 102, PASSWORD 2802
[Hwang chuckles softly]
[religious chants playing over speakers]
Let's begin the prayer.
[chanting prayers]
When you sleep,
does the past still haunt you?
Yeah, sometimes.
And the sudden shortness of breath...
Does that keep happening?
I'm not asking as your uncle-in-law,
but as a licensed psychiatrist.
I just want to help you.
Yes, sometimes.
Before it destroys you,
you have to let it go.
It's been ten years
since your parents passed,
and you can't keep blaming yourself.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Good.
[chanting continues]
[scoffs]
[gong sounding]
[indistinct chatter]
It's time for the shares to be sorted.
I'm not sure we can
delay this much longer,
or else some might get the wrong idea
about who gets what.
Do as you please, Auntie.
The whole family's meeting for dinner.
Aren't you going?
Unfortunately, I can't. I have plans.
All right, I'll be in touch.
Did you wait in the car?
I made sure to stay out of sight,
since your relatives
hate seeing me around.
Did they try to console you
again this year?
It must be getting annoying.
It's expected. That's how they are.
The elders are like snakes in the grass,
watching me carefully
to see if the loss of my parents
is still affecting me,
especially that man... [scoffs]
Calling himself my uncle
and pretending to care about me.
Always ensuring I don't forget.
Anyways, let's go eat.
I'll tell them to prepare your meal.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm unable to join you today.
I apologize.
I hope you understand.
All right.
I was really hoping
I wouldn't be eating alone today.
[in Korean] All is ready.
-[knife slashing]
-[groaning]
[Cheongri grunts]
[man groaning]
[knife slashing]
[panting lightly]
[chuckles softly]
[breath trembling]
Insert it deep in one breath.
[Yohan's aunt] You wretched bitch.
How dare you?
I should have thrown you out
while I could.
You had no power to begin with.
Young Master would have never allowed it.
Have you told him the truth about...
who his real mother is?
That the filthy blood of a lowly bitch
like you is running through his veins?
Does he know?
It's Master Yohan
who single-handedly built this company.
Someone who thinks they can take it
because of family-owned shares
is most likely the lowlier bitch, I think.
[thudding]
[whimpering]
[sighs]
-[knife slashing]
-[screaming]
The only person our young master
could ever open his heart up to
was me.
He was alone and tormented by those
who called themselves his family.
Which explains why he hated
whenever I left him.
You might have fooled him,
but I know you've always exploited him
for your own personal gain.
[spits]
So in order to make sure I stayed,
he crept in one night and poured mercury
into each of my eyes to make me blind.
I know that was his way
of expressing his love to me,
and I will always be
grateful to him for it.
-[♪ dance music playing]
-[firecrackers exploding]
-[tires screeching]
-[women exclaim]
Hey!
Why don't you watch where you're going?
I didn't hit you, so back the fuck off!
-[Seongyu] Oh shit, hey.
-Let me go!
Stupid ho!
-Hey!
-I'll fucking kill you.
Dokyung!
Okay, okay, okay. Okay.
-[woman] Stop!
-Hold on. Wait. Come on, dude.
[Seongyu] Wait.
Okay.
Hey, we're here to drink
and have a good time, remember?
All right.
Forget her. Let's go!
-[woman] Psycho!
-Come on!
She's crazy. Don't worry about her.
What the fuck are you looking at?
[laughs]
Hey, I hope you know
I went all out for tonight.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Hey, there's no friend like me, right?
[continues talking indistinctly]
Here.
Page 42.
Fuck yeah! Let's party!
-[♪ techno dance music playing]
-[crowd cheering]
[music fades out]
[whispering] Shit.
[panting]
[laughing]
My friend mentioned
he saw a fucking weirdo stalking me.
Didn't realize it was you, delivery guy.
Good to finally meet you.
How's life?
What do you mean? Like, how have I been?
While I was rotting in prison for you...
what were you doing?
Oh...
You know, drinking and partying,
screwing bitches, surviving. [laughs]
[sighs]
Chu Nayoung.
You remember her?
Chu Nayoung?
Oh... Oh, her. [laughs]
Did you think I'd be crying every day
over that girl, full of regret,
tormented by guilt and unable to sleep?
That what you wanted?
You already did that for me.
And now I don't need you anymore.
[Taejoong sighs]
[men yelling, grunting]
Dokyung.
-Go wait inside for me.
-Sure.
[grunting continues]
[groaning]
You're done.
[thud]
Yes, I'll be at the funeral hall tomorrow.
I picked this out for you.
You didn't have to do that.
I'm an adult now.
Taking care of you
is one of my few pleasures.
[Yohan chuckles softly]
By the way, I heard there was an accident
with the elders and my aunt.
During the memorial dinner,
a massive fire broke out.
Really?
I guess these things happen, right?
BAEK DOKYUNG
[cell phone vibrating]
[Dokyung] You won't believe this.
I caught my avatar
and locked him in a room.
[chuckles softly]
I was wondering who'd win.
I'm surprised.
There's something
I'm curious about, Mr. An.
How'd that bastard know
exactly where to find me?
[chuckles softly]
Cough up the money you were paid
while I'm still asking nicely.
You did manage to catch him.
So I should give you a refund.
[Dokyung laughing]
But send it to my account
instead of my father's.
And you don't care
if I kill the guy myself, do you?
Be my guest.
What a disappointing finale.
Oh, tell me, did anyone survive the fire?
The entire home was burnt to a crisp.
So it looks like there are no survivors.
That's the best news
I've heard in a while.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[♪ muffled music playing]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
We're going shopping tomorrow, right?
I wanna go.
[mumbles]
Have you...
ever killed a dog?
Like... [howling]
-[laughing]
-What?
A dog? You ever killed one?
Actually, over there...
There's a rabid dog inside.
He's disobedient. Stupid dog.
Let's put him out of its misery.
Yeah?
Yeah, come on. This'll be fun, all right?
Fuck, yeah! Let's kill this dog!
Get up! Come on.
-[laughing]
-Stop!
This isn't funny. Knock it off!
Just take me shopping instead.
Dumb bitch. [chuckles]
[man] Pour me a glass.
-You have to mix it first.
-Any good?
-[Seongyu] Take this one.
-[laughter]
-Let's do it.
-All right, let's hurry up and drink!
[all cheering]
Throw it back. Chug, chug, chug!
Oh, yeah! Drink up!
Good shit, huh?
[woman laughs]
-I'm already starting to feel it.
-Yeah!
Holy shit!
Hell yeah!
-Hey, hold on, get off!
-[woman] Baby!
Mr. Shin. How many strokes
are you gonna shoot?
I'm gonna break a hundred! [laughing]
[woman] I'm gonna have some more.
[Noh Yongsik]
It's around here somewhere...
Is it this way?
[sirens approaching]
Cops.
-Come on, hurry!
-Shit!
[policeman] Gather round, everyone.
Whoa.
Head to the back of the building,
split up in teams of three
and surround them.
-[policeman 2] Yes, sir.
-Okay, You guys are with me.
Oh, jeez.
-We have to find Taejoong fast.
-Yeah.
I'll go and check the boat
over there, okay?
-I'll look in here.
-Sounds good.
-Check everywhere.
-Okay.
-Be careful.
-Yeah.
Taejoong? Are you here?
Taejoong?
We need to discuss the next round
of investment.
Come on. I've been giving you
whatever you asked for.
-[laughter]
-I thought we were friends.
That's right.
-So be a pal, okay?
-[sirens wailing]
[woman] What's that sound?
Cops are here?
Oh, shit. Hey, make sure
he doesn't do anything crazy.
[breathing heavily]
All right. Get the fuck
out of my way, assholes!
Hey! Hey!
Step aside, before I lose it.
Move!
I'm sorry,
but there's a dress code to get in.
HWANG ILGUK
KOREAN POLICE
And what makes you think I give a shit?
Don't be rude, okay?
We're just looking for this guy.
Satisfied?
Appreciate your cooperation.
Hey.
I don't want to make a scene, detective.
[laughing]
Listen to me, you piece of shit.
I've heard of you,
but you don't know what I'm capable of.
Enough with the tough guy act.
I'll be quick.
Find that asshole now!
-[policemen] Yes, sir.
-[man] Follow me.
I'll start looking for them in here.
Oh, wait, wait.
You go check around the ships
at the dock, okay?
I'll handle this area.
[sighs]
He's so good at following orders.
You fucking gold-diggers.
Am I a fucking bank to you?
How dare you?
Stupid hoes.
[sighs] You're all the fucking same.
-[breathing heavily]
-[line ringing]
Where are you?
I'm so bored of these bitches.
Let's kill that delivery guy.
[Seongyu] Hold off on that.
The cops are here.
You serious?
[laughing]
All right, keep yourself
out of trouble. Stay put.
No, you're not the boss of me.
Hey! Listen to me.
Just stay there. Don't move.
Wait, wait, wait.
I told you he's not here.
-He might be in the other rooms.
-Out of my way!
He never came in here.
He might be over there.
-I need to confirm that.
-He's not here.
Come on. Trust me.
I think I saw him hiding there.
I swear, across the hall over there.
Yeah.
Off limits.
-[woman grunting]
-Didn't you hear me?
This area is restricted to everyone.
-Really?
-Including you.
[people exclaiming]
Get the fuck out of my way!
Goddamn.
-Get a hold of yourself.
-My friend's in there.
-No, she's not.
-[cries out]
[woman] What's your problem?
[grunting]
[exhales heavily]
[door opens]
[grunts]
Delivery guy?
Where is he?
Shit. Where did I put that fucker?
Fuck me.
Oh, shit.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Let's go.
-Stop right there.
-Huh?
Officer Yang.
Park Taejoong.
You have to leave. Go!
Noh Yongsik!
If you take one more step,
I'll have to take you back to prison.
Whether I'm free or locked up,
it makes no difference.
Don't lie to me.
Do you really want
to abandon your daughter again?
Don't bring her into this.
Park Taejoong.
I get it. Believe me, I do.
But you can't do it this way.
Let me help you.
-We'll go through all of--
-Officer Yang.
If you truly want to help him,
the best thing for you to do right now
is to let us go.
Come on.
We have to go.
Hey!
Holy shit!
Whoo! Look who it is!
Everybody's here!
Park Taejoong! I've finally found you.
[laughing, whoops]
What are you standing around for? Come on.
[Cheolhwan] Detective.
We need to get out of here. Run!
[Cheolhwan] Detective Hwang!
-Eunbi.
-Where do you think you're going?
Hey, I'll do it! Stay back!
[grunting]
You fucking bitch!
[crowd murmuring]
Where the fuck is that
delivery cocksucker?
-[bystanders screaming]
-Useless fucks!
-[grunts] Goddamn it.
-[woman screams]
How could you let
that delivery fucker get away?
Fuck!
Where the fuck is he?
-Hey!
-Hey.
Did you miss me?
Of course I did.
So what brings you all the way here?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry for crashing
your place like this.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Is that your dad?
Don't worry. I'll explain later.
You can head inside.
Once Taejoong gets here,
we'll follow you in.
There he is.
-Okay. Whatever you say.
-[motorcycle approaching]
-Door's unlocked.
-Yeah.
He's here.
You okay?
Let's go inside.
[loud bang]
-You've got to be kidding me.
-[gas hissing]
Eunbi, can you take him inside?
-Sure.
-I'll take care of this.
[Eunbi] Come on.
[sighs in exasperation]
Just what I needed.
[door opens, shuts]
Can I play with this one, too?
Sure. You can play with that one. [laughs]
I'm letting you play with it
because you ate all your food.
[door opens]
Go. Get out.
[Taejoong on recording] Chu Nayoung.
[sighs] You remember her?
[Dokyung] Chu Nayoung?
Oh... Oh, her. [laughs]
Did you think I'd be crying every day
over that girl, full of regret,
tormented by guilt and unable to sleep?
That what you wanted?
You already did that for me.
[laughs]
BUSAN BUS TERMINAL
[beeping]
Hmm. You're up already?
I owe you.
-Gimme some money and we'll call it even.
-I mean it.
I can't thank you enough.
Yeah.
Sure, whatever.
I'm going to the mechanic
to pick up the old man.
You can chill here.
[exhales]
Make yourself at home, okay?
Sure. Thanks.
Hey, stop being so weird.
-Wait. Hold on.
-Yeah.
-What?
-Explain yourself.
Who on earth is that guy?
He's nobody.
Ah, shit.
-Are you two dating?
-No, it's not like that.
Then what is it like?
[sighs]
Well, actually, he's an escapee.
[laughs] An escapee?
So where did he escape from?
Your heart?
-Ah, shit.
-Uh-uh-uh...
Ex-boyfriend?
Ever since he got out,
he's been acting really fucking weird.
-I think he needs help.
-Why are you avoiding all my questions?
Give me the key.
Fine. Here you go.
He's a strange guy.
I think he might be lonely.
He should find someone.
-[scoffs]
-[Eunbi] You're so annoying.
[engine starts]
-Wow, it smells good.
-Here you go.
Thanks.
Can I get another?
-Hotteok is my daughter's favorite.
-You got it.
-I appreciate it.
-Sure. Enjoy.
You didn't need to come
all the way out here.
What were you thinking,
driving a broken car?
What if you got into an accident?
Um, I got this for you, if you want it.
I'm sorry I made you uncomfortable again.
I mean, you already got it, so...
They said the car
will be fixed by tomorrow.
[sighs]
How's Taejoong doing?
He's fine, okay?
So he's a pretty good guy
once you get to know him, don't you think?
Yeah. He actually seems like a decent man.
All right. Come on, let's head back.
I'll drive so you can eat that.
Who the fuck are these stupid idiots,
anyway? Huh?
My guys are looking for them now,
so be patient.
You should go out there
and find them yourself, asshole!
[Seongyu scoffs]
Sure.
Okay.
Hey, let's grab something to eat.
[man] Yeah, I'm starving.
I'm sick of this shit.
Wait a minute.
Where's my phone?
[line ringing]
-Yes.
-Hey, it's me.
I hate that I have to ask you this.
It was you, right?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Did you sneak him out because
you didn't want to give me a refund?
You wouldn't do that, would you?
Stooping that low isn't quite your style.
Ah.
So it hasn't been decided
whose prize it is.
What prize?
What the fuck are you talking about?
[line disconnects]
What a smug little shithead.
Looks like he's got friends.
Well played, Park Taejoong. [chuckles]
So you're telling me
this is the guy you took the fall for?
What a terrible person.
[sighs]
Did you find any proof there?
All I did was ask him questions.
Like, "How's life?"
And what was the point in asking him that?
Bet his answer was bullshit.
You know what?
I think I...
I just want him to apologize.
Yeah.
He needs to say sorry.
He owes you that much.
You'll get an apology.
I promise you.
We'll make sure he apologizes.
I'll help you with everything.
Don't worry, okay?
-[sighs]
-It's all right.
So that guy's an escaped convict?
We'll need to discuss
how much extra this will cost.
All you think about is money, don't you?
Greedy bitch.
[drill whirring]
Give him a good show.
Son of a-- [grunts]
[men grunting]
[laughing]
[camera shutter clicks]
Rounding. 9:00 p.m. tee off.
SHARE POST
Don't be late.
I'll be waiting, delivery guy.
The Manipulated